{
    "subject": "resource/WarpSpeed",
    "predicate": "property/platforms",
    "object": "resource/Sega_Genesis",
    "human_readable": "WarpSpeed is a platform for Sega Genesis.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9448351263999939,
            "question": "Is WarpSpeed compatible with the Sega Genesis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8605198264122009,
            "question": "Name a platform that utilizes WarpSpeed."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6987651586532593,
            "question": "Who developed the platform known as WarpSpeed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5763295292854309,
            "question": "What is WarpSpeed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4955596625804901,
            "question": "For which gaming console was WarpSpeed developed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.484695702791214,
            "question": "What kind of software is WarpSpeed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4510820508003235,
            "question": "What are some of the features offered by WarpSpeed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.403164803981781,
            "question": "How does WarpSpeed work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3216715455055237,
            "question": "Why was WarpSpeed created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26391932368278503,
            "question": "What games could potentially run on WarpSpeed?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=WarpSpeed is a platform for Sega Genesis.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7491_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why was WarpSpeed created?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7491_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does WarpSpeed work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7491_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the features offered by WarpSpeed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7491_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7491_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7491_140.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7491_147.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7491_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7491_166.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7491_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7491_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7491_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7491_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7491_53.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the provided context information, I can confirm that the triple \"WarpSpeed is a platform for Sega Genesis\" is indeed supported by the documents.\n\nHere's the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that WarpSpeed was released for the Sega Genesis (also known as Sega Mega Drive) platform, thus supporting the statement that WarpSpeed is a platform game for Sega Genesis."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "WarpSpeed is not a platform, but rather a game released for the Sega Genesis console.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}